https://www.oc-usa.com/privacy-policy-2/

The Beaches and Towns Network
Beaches and Towns Network, Inc. 37232 Lighthouse Road, Suite 230Selbyville, Delaware 19975
We respect your privacy! Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you provide either via email or one of our on-line forms will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don’t hesitate to let us know. You may email us at Bill [at] OCtheBeach [dot] com.
Resale or disclosure of information to third parties:
OC-USA.com does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms or email lists.
Third party links and/or vendors:
OC-USA.com provides links to other websites that provide information for the use of our visitors. We also serve advertising and offer products made available by other parties via affiliate and or partnership agreements. Should you visit another web site through a link provided by OC-USA.com or enter into a transaction provided by another party, you will be leaving OC-USA.com and we urge you to read the privacy policy of that party.
For example,we may have ads served onto our site by an e-commerce vendor. To view their privacy statement, please visit their web site.
Browser information collected on the website:
OC-USA.com analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of the information provided on this website. Our website logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with individuals who browse this site.
Use of cookies:
We do not use cookies on this site. However, some of the sites we link to may use cookies. Again, should you visit another web site through a link provided by OC-USA.com or enter into a transaction provided by another party, you will be leaving OC-USA.com and we urge you to read the privacy policy of that party.
Privacy of our email lists:
OC-USA.com does not currently maintain email lists. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease the email addresses of individuals who email us with a question or a comment. However, some of the sites we link to may maintain email lists. Again, should you visit another web site through a link provided by OC-USA.com or enter into a transaction provided by another party, you will be leaving OC-USA.com and we urge you to read the privacy policy of that party.
Hotel reservations fulfillment provided by the Booking.com Affiliate Network.
Search hotels and more...
